Kyle Lorenzo: You did.
Kyle Lorenzo: Hi, Kyle, how's it going?
Cal: Hey Kyle, how are you?
Kyle Lorenzo: Doing good, dude. How are you doing?
Cal: I'm good.
Kyle Lorenzo: Good to hear, good to hear. Hopefully the week's been going well for you.
Cal: Yeah, I hope yours has been too. No, just packing and…
Cal: Working, always.
Kyle Lorenzo: Hacking, where are you going?
Cal: Just moving.
Kyle Lorenzo: Oh, gotcha, just moving. Yeah. Okay, I thought you were going on a trip or something.
Cal: That would be cool.
Kyle Lorenzo: I'll deserve one, huh?
Kyle Lorenzo: But cool. Cool, thanks for getting the, thanks for getting that sheet over to me yesterday. I went ahead and updated the, the showroom website. I'm sorry, my computer's having, like, a weird monitor issue going on right now. Let me see if I can,
Kyle Lorenzo: That's apologies.
Kyle Lorenzo: Started… there we go.
Kyle Lorenzo: All right, but yeah, let me, let me share my screen. We can take a look at the, at the showroom website again with the, with all of those things updated and added to it. I updated the…
Kyle Lorenzo: the hero to be a little bit more, like, B-roll-y. I found those… I did find those, those… those Google Drives that Tom sent over, so I did get a lot of the actual live, live stuff up on there. And then, in addition to that, we did get the, materials for these, and then, so…
Cal: I tried to give you so many countries, and as I was typing them, they're all from the same countries, and I was like, okay.
Cal: Stone only comes from so many places.
Kyle Lorenzo: Right, right, right, right. So, these are the, these are the ones that we got on there. And then, would you happen to have, like, the, let me see if it was on here, but the,
Kyle Lorenzo: They would, they would need to link to all of these. Yeah, if you had, do you know, if you have, like, a good, like, close-up picture that I'd be able to put on each of these ones, for example?
Cal: So, they're all exotics, to be completely honest with you. I basically, for reference, I basically have hundreds of thousands of dollars worth of exotic stones here, but that is one of the biggest draws of people coming into the showroom, is the fact that, like, a handful of these stones,
Cal: if you were to Google them, you can't get the exact vein of that slab, so I'd prefer for them to not…
Cal: to show a photo of it, because, again, like, even when we render it, it's almost impossible to render, because you can Google that slab, you'll see 100 photos of it, but getting the exact
Cal: that I have is…
Kyle Lorenzo: Right.
Cal: we don't have it, so we kind of have to maybe think about something different there. I don't know if we can be… if we can think of, like I said, we can either use a more generic photo, or we can, like… like a more Googleable generic photo, or something, but, like.
Cal: the exact slabs that we have here, like, I don't want the actual slab photos up.
Kyle Lorenzo: Gotcha. Right, yeah, because it's gonna be… it's gonna be different every time, especially with, like, all the different cuts. Okay, I'm thinking then, because I can maybe do, like…
Kyle Lorenzo: a… almost like a slideshow where it'll show different veins, but again, at the same time, it might just be one of those, like, if you know, you know type of things, where if you're looking for it, you're generally gonna know what you're kind of getting into. Let me play with that one for a little.
Cal: Okay.
Kyle Lorenzo: And I'll kind of think of something else that we can maybe do for that.
Cal: The other thing is, is I can give you maybe some of, like.
Cal: the furniture vendors we can use, and you can maybe Google through them and see, like, where they source material, because we have a lot of furniture vendors who source from, like, Thailand and Indonesia and places like that, and then, like, you can figure out, like, a fun way to call out, like, sourcing and stuff, but again, we can't call out
Cal: the actual vendor names. So that's where we kind of get stuck, is if we can find out a cool way of, like, calling out where we source material from, then.
Kyle Lorenzo: Right.
Cal: we can use that. We just can't necessarily specifically call out vendors. We have certain vendors we can call out, like Buster and Punch, which is, like,
Cal: like a light switch type company that we use, and a lighting company, they're so popular that, since we rep for them, we can put their brand all over it. Same thing with our cabinet companies. But other types, when they're so competitive, we just can't.
Cal: You know?
Kyle Lorenzo: Right.
Kyle Lorenzo: Oh, man, I'm wondering… do you know how specific it gets with some of the… with some of the sourcing? I'm wondering if we can put maybe, like.
Kyle Lorenzo: A picture of the location, if they came from a very specific.
Cal: 100%. They're all incredibly specific. If you… so if you take any of the names that I gave you, if you put them into chat or something like that, or even Google Gemini, if you type them, they'll tell you the exact province that they're from. So, like, most of the Calicutas come from actual Calicutta, a lot of the araboscatos will come from Tuscany and stuff like that, so they'll.
Kyle Lorenzo: Right.
Cal: the regions.
Kyle Lorenzo: Oh, that's perfect. Okay, I'll do that. I think that would be cool, because then I can just put, like, a really nice snapshot of, like, that geo, or whatever that comes from. Tuscany can have, like, really cool, like, Tuscan, like, mountain range, or just something cool that…
Kyle Lorenzo: you know, if they know, they'll know, and then if they see that picture, they'll… they can kind of at least get, like, a visual of kind of where it's coming from, the heritage of it. I think that might… that might work there.
Cal: They come from Zoho.
Kyle Lorenzo: Give that a try.
Cal: Yeah, I would say, honestly, even, like I said, even if you just Google Gemini that shit, like, it'll give you pretty accurate information on it.
Kyle Lorenzo: Okay, perfect. Okay, that's perfect. That sounds fun. Let me, let me go do that, and then, I'll see if I can get that updated today. I'll try something new on that. That sounds… that sounds pretty interesting. I think I could do something cool there.
Kyle Lorenzo: But cool. Yeah, outside of that, the rest of the, the rest of the website, we have just updated with the new assets, of everything there. The cabinetry, we're gonna go in and do the same thing here.
Kyle Lorenzo: With the cabinetry, do you want… we do want to have the vendor and all that info on here as well, or do we.
Cal: Yeah, I think for the cabinetry, let's actually try and focus on the vendors, because of the fact that we have one, two, three, four, five… we have five vendors that we're using, and they're incredibly popular, and all of them are going to be doing marketing for us. And we're even fine linking into all of their websites as well, so if people want to, like, go directly into their website and look at, like.
Cal: all of the, like, the cabinet door information on their website, if they want to go straight in, like, if we want to link in, we totally can, right? So, I'm fine with putting, like, the actual cabinet door, or, like, the actual cabinet manufacturer information on, because that's a huge sell point for us. They all market for us, same thing, we're all on, like, their Instagram accounts and stuff like that. And it's a big draw. Like, our German cabinetry company, they're, like, one of the
Cal: top 10 German manufacturers in the world, so again, it's a pretty large draw. So generally speaking, I would say for, like, the cabinetry part, instead of focusing on, like, the door style or the door coloring, since they all kind of carry similar door styles and similar colors, it would be easier to focus on the manufacturer, because at that point, a lot of people are after the manufacturer. Like, when people are going to pronor.
Cal: they're specifically going for that German kitchen. If people are going to Fabbywood, they're specifically going because of the brand Fabbywood, and then same thing with Eclipse. So, if we could maybe, like, zone in on, like, that feature from them, that would probably be a pretty, like, a good sell point.
Kyle Lorenzo: Right. Okay, perfect, yeah. That'll be really good on the SEO side, because that'll help drill down, those particular brands. I know everybody's… everybody usually starts with the brand anyway, and then they kind of drill down from there, so that's perfect.
Cal: Yeah, and I'm sure each of the websites, too, like, Pronorm, for sure, has one of the better websites, Fabbywood has one of the better websites, and then Eclipse, those are our top 3 out of the bunch.
Cal: So if we have anything from, like, their website that we want to use for marketing, we can also use that too. So we kind of have, like, options with that. So, yeah. And then I can also tell you which of the kitchens is which, which technically the ProNorm kitchen isn't built yet, but, gotcha. Yeah. So, but yeah, we can use any of their stuff as well.
Kyle Lorenzo: Perfect.
Kyle Lorenzo: Alright, sounds good. Cool.
Cal: Do you have, by chance, in all of this, do you have… do you have the black kitchen in there at all? Like, a black backlit kitchen anywhere?
Kyle Lorenzo: Let me see… with the ones that I had in there, I think I used pretty much all the B-roll on this.
Cal: So I wonder if I haven't… we might have not photographed it yet.
Cal: I'll have to check the
Cal: I'll check the drop box and see, because we maybe haven't photographed it yet. I have one more kitchen up that is… I haven't seen on here yet. It's black, and it's entirely backlit with Crystallo, and that's also a Fabbywood kitchen.
Kyle Lorenzo: Oh, nice.
Cal: So that.
Kyle Lorenzo: Oh, beautiful.
Cal: That one is super pretty, and then I'm in the process of building a custom walnut one, which we can photograph in hopefully the next couple weeks, too, so…
Kyle Lorenzo: Nice. Oh, beautiful. Okay, perfect. Yeah, I think the back of the kitchen would be super, super cool here.
Cal: Yeah.
Kyle Lorenzo: But… Right. Okay, perfect.
Kyle Lorenzo: I think that should pretty much cover the rest of it, then.
Cal: For the scrolling… scroll down a little.
Kyle Lorenzo: Yeah.
Cal: The… a little more…
Cal: For this part, this horizontal bar, I would prefer for it not to be showroom pieces.
Kyle Lorenzo: Gotcha.
Cal: should I put there? Like, what else do you think.
Kyle Lorenzo: Goodness.
Cal: if I have our team photograph stuff. Because, like I said, I'm still trying… I still want to minimize what people see on the website.
Kyle Lorenzo: Right.
Cal: So, what else do you think, if I have my photo team take photographs for you, what else do you think we could use in this? Like, whether it's video footage, whether it's photos, what else do you think would show well in this setting?
Kyle Lorenzo: Yeah, I do kind of want to reuse that Netflix-style accordion that we had on the original page, however…
Cal: Photos?
Kyle Lorenzo: cent.
Cal: Or…
Kyle Lorenzo: Yeah, with the content there, because I wouldn't want to show too much of the… too much of, like, the panoramic of, like, all the different shots there.
Cal: I can also
Cal: photos of lighting, I can get you photos of some of the slabs, if you want some of the slabs, and I can also do, like, mood board photos of, like, tile samples, things along those lines. Like, you know how people do, like, tile mood board type of things?
Kyle Lorenzo: Yeah.
Cal: Pinterest and stuff, so if there's something like that that you want, if you have, like, an inspiration photo or something like that, I can do that.
Kyle Lorenzo: too.
Kyle Lorenzo: Okay, I'll send over what I think I… what we could… what we could do here. I think a mood board is a really good idea, that way…
Cal: Okay.
Kyle Lorenzo: you know, people can kind of see that, and then they can almost just basically get inspired. They can, like, look at… they can maybe even… it can even… maybe even be interactive, where they click into it, and then we can kind of curate based off of the type of slabs that might, fit into that, you know, that aesthetic that they're looking for.
Cal: Yeah, send me…
Kyle Lorenzo: works.
Cal: Yeah, send me a picture, like, 2 or 3 pictures of what, like, the ideal mood board would look like in that section, like, photograph-wise, and then I'll have my design team put, like, a few things together, and then I'll have our photo team take pictures of it for you, and then we can send it over.
Kyle Lorenzo: Okay, sounds good. Cool, I'll send over what I've got then on that side. I'll go ahead and I already have everything that I need to get this published up to showroom.byblocks.com, so I'll get that up and published today, that way, if you want to kind of circulate it around the team.
Kyle Lorenzo: We can get, like, a mock of that section that I'm gonna be building out for them. They can kind of improvise it and see what they'll… they'll need to…
Kyle Lorenzo: Have I helped on the issue to make it look good on that end. And then I think we'll just… we'll get that up there, and we'll take it from there.
Cal: Okay, and then what about… what are the rest of our tabs right now?
Kyle Lorenzo: So we've got the stone, the cabinetry, the tile, and the sourcing. Outside of those ones, it's pretty lean. It just goes straight into, basically everything just goes straight into the,
Kyle Lorenzo: the booking thing, or the requested introduction, which is gonna be that form that's just gonna send to your, your email. Same one as the office one.
Cal: Okay, so I think for sure, I like the appointments one, I like the cabinetry one. I don't know if we need individuals for, like, tile and stone, to be honest.
Kyle Lorenzo: Right. I do want to have them… I want to have something there, at least just for SEO. Okay.
Cal: Is it good for marketing?
Kyle Lorenzo: Yeah, it's good for marketing, too.
Kyle Lorenzo: It could be, like you said, since they are gonna be exotics, we don't have to… we don't necessarily have to be too…
Kyle Lorenzo: But just having some sort of… some sort of content on there, just for the, just for the…
Cal: And same thing, do you want us to take photos for these, or are we using… what are we using? Like, generic photos? What are we…
Kyle Lorenzo: Yeah.
Cal: photos.
Kyle Lorenzo: Yeah, with the cabinetry, definitely, we'll do… we'll definitely do the… based off the brands, with the cabinetry, we'll do the photos there.
Cal: the top.
Kyle Lorenzo: Island Stone.
Cal: same thing, tile, we can either… the tile, it's so… well, like, Zooliege, obviously, like, that's a type of tile, the stone mosaics, so same thing, we can put in, like, general brands and stuff that we carry, or general types.
Kyle Lorenzo: Right.
Cal: Or we can just pick out, like, we can pick out, like, our top 10 or 12 tiles, and then have you upload pictures of the tiles in, and just not connect the brands in.
Kyle Lorenzo: Gotcha.
Cal: So that's.
Kyle Lorenzo: I think that's.
Cal: super popular to do on a lot of, like, websites. If you go to places like, do you know what Bodega Tile is?
Kyle Lorenzo: Not off the top of my head, but…
Cal: Yeah, their website's shit, but whatever, it's a good example.
Kyle Lorenzo: Yeah.
Cal: Okay, so Bodega?
Kyle Lorenzo: Oh, let's see…
Cal: They sell all of their tile, but they buy from other vendors, okay? Gotcha. So when you click on their tile,
Cal: anything. Okay, so this is not tile that they make, it's something that they buy from somewhere else.
Kyle Lorenzo: Gotcha.
Cal: They… so they have all of this tile, but they're buying it from somewhere else. It's not actually from Bodega. They don't make it. So they rename it. They give it a totally different name, a totally different SKU. I don't have the time.
Kyle Lorenzo: That would be just…
Cal: Yeah, they just.
Kyle Lorenzo: Just white label it, okay.
Cal: Correct, they white-label it. Gotcha. So, I can give you a bunch of tile in each category, if you can give me the categories you want, and then we can give you tiles from all the companies we source from. You just have to figure out how you want to label it, because we are not…
Kyle Lorenzo: there.
Cal: And we can still put a name on it, like, we can put the name on it, you just can't link in, again, the vendor name. Right. So, if the tile is called Sky Blue Mosaic, you could call it Blue Mosaic, and then just don't say it's from Tile Club.
Kyle Lorenzo: Right, right, right, gotcha.
Cal: When the client comes in, I'm still gonna tell them it's from fucking Tile Club, but I don't need them to literally hit a link that goes to Tile Club.
Kyle Lorenzo: Right, gotcha. I wouldn't want to make those… I wouldn't want to go ahead and name them for you. I mean, we could give it a try.
Cal: Yeah, no, I can name them. I can totally name them, and then I can… I can name them all for you, and then I can link… I'll link them into the actual websites, that way you can use the best photos off of their websites, because that's what we do for ourselves, is, like, we pull their photos directly off Tile Bar, Tile Club, and stuff like that, because that's… we're trade vendors for all those guys. But you just can't put, like, the… you can't literally use their name on it, that's the only rule.
Cal: So, like, you can… I can give you the name, like, Blue Sky Mosaic, you can snip the photo straight off their website, all of that's legal, you just can't literally link in their website to our website.
Kyle Lorenzo: Right. Okay, perfect.
Cal: So…
Kyle Lorenzo: Yeah, well, I'll try to make it a little less, in-depth, maybe, and then we'll just try to get, like, just the very high level, and then we… so we don't have to go too deep into the whole, like, we're not just creating a whole dictionary of new names and everything.
Cal: Yeah
Cal: Yeah, it's honestly, it's pretty easy. We… we keep them pretty much the same names as what the vendors keep them as, because we need to still be able to look them up. Right. And we, honestly, we give the clients the names of the tiles, and we link them in our own presentations, so, like, the client can follow the link to Tile Club's website, but we just can't link them on, like, an actual physical website.
Cal: That's all. So, like, we can link them on our paperwork, we just can't link them on a website.
Kyle Lorenzo: Right, gotcha. Understood. Okay.
Kyle Lorenzo: Yeah, let's do that. I like spreadsheets. Spreadsheets have been very, very helpful.
Cal: I can just add a tab, but, on the showroom spreadsheet I already started, can you just write down which categories you want?
Kyle Lorenzo: Yeah, I'll do that, I'll make a.
Cal: leash you want.
Cal: Like, marble mosaic, you want.
Cal: Like, just write down what tab, like, what,
Kyle Lorenzo: Like, categories.
Cal: Yeah, yeah, just write what category. You don't even have to make the boxes, I'll make you all the boxes, but just write down what categories you want.
Kyle Lorenzo: Got you, I got you.
Kyle Lorenzo: Alright, I'll make the, I'll make those boxes, I'll just have them added to one of these new sheets, and then, we can just start adding on here.
Cal: Yeah, perfect, and I'll just throw a bunch of stuff in there. It'll be super easy.
Kyle Lorenzo: Cool. Alright. Very cool.
Kyle Lorenzo: Cool, then I think we're in a pretty good spot. I'll send over… I'll… like I said, I'll get this link published, I'll make the… I'll add the categories to that spreadsheet, I'll play with that locations thing here for the… for the map again, make this look a little bit more like… I think it'll look so cool with, like.
Kyle Lorenzo: this having, like, Tuscany and, like, all that, and, like, different pictures of different cuts of Italy. That's gonna look super cool. I'm gonna try something interesting there, so I'll… I'm excited to get that one up.
Cal: Cool. And then the sourcing page, what is the sourcing page supposed to be?
Kyle Lorenzo: So I'm thinking it could just be this map, but maybe in greater detail. Maybe this map, like, on its own isolated page, and then with, like, an accompanying list down here below, so that they can see the entire picture all at once. But it would be reusing the same components.
Cal: Okay.
Cal: Very cool. Okay. I think on the appointments page, I think somewhere I have to have, like, a process paragraph, like, somewhere, so people know, like.
Kyle Lorenzo: Gotcha.
Cal: What we're capable of selling, or, like, what our process is,
Kyle Lorenzo: Yeah, I just…
Cal: I don't know where, but somewhere we have to have, like, some type of thing of being like, you can come in to purchase this way, this way, or that way, you know? I don't know what. Right.
Kyle Lorenzo: Gotcha.
Cal: 3D.
Kyle Lorenzo: Gotcha. Okay, I'll shoot over some, some, some cool process pages and stuff like that in the meantime as well. That way maybe we can, just pull from one, kind of tailor from it.
Cal: I don't.
Kyle Lorenzo: That way it'd be like.
Cal: huge processing, but just something, because for reference, for the showroom, I'm selling to contractors, I'm selling to designers, and I'm selling to the public, right? So I have, like, multiple fronts that we're selling on, so I need to appeal to being like, oh, I can sell direct.
Kyle Lorenzo: She's like, yeah.
Cal: Yeah, I can sell direct to the client if you're looking to buy tile, if you're looking to buy, cabinetry, or anything along those lines, but if you're a designer and you need help in the process to sell to your client or something like that, we're open to talking to you as well. So, we just need some type of, like, appeal, I guess, would be in there, where, like, if you're a contractor, a designer, or just an everyday client, please, like, reach out to us. We're willing to help.
Cal: Like, multiple different groups of people, you know?
Kyle Lorenzo: Right.
Cal: it's not just made for a client, it's also made for the industry. Same thing with, like, realtors, too. Like, if you're selling and you're trying to get that client to buy the house, and they need a helping hand, like, we can… we can help you finish that sale. So, I just need to get that point across to people somewhere.
Kyle Lorenzo: I'm wondering, then, if… would you be opposed to if we had specific pages for each one? It doesn't have to be directly accessible through the navigation, but say, for example, if they… if they clicked, like, about us, then there would be kind of, like, a different… almost like a picker, where you'd be able to choose, like, hey, which one of these best describes what you're… what you're doing?
Cal: I'm totally open to that. That's how our main, like, five blocks website is set up, where you.
Kyle Lorenzo: Yeah.
Cal: like, if you're an interior designer, an architect, or, like, a home buyer, I'm totally fine with that, because then we can explain to each of the people, like, how we would be doing it.
Kyle Lorenzo: Exactly. Yeah. Okay, perfect. Cool, I'll… I'll…
Kyle Lorenzo: I'll go forward with something like that, then, as just the basic plan, and then I'll just get, like, a quick little thing, so that way they don't have to, like, keep fishing for info or anything like that. They'll just be able to kind of pick their industry, like, hey, what best describes you, and then they'll see a little bit more info, based off what they want there.
Cal: Cool.
Kyle Lorenzo: Cool.
Kyle Lorenzo: Alright, I think we're… we're in a good spot. I'll go ahead and give this all up and published. I'm gonna start chipping away at it already pretty much as soon as I get off here. Maybe you'll be able to see my edits on the live side as I kind of get through. But, yeah, I'll send you the link here in about, like, 20 minutes, as soon as it finishes publishing, and then we'll just kind of keep collaborating on it throughout
Kyle Lorenzo: Yeah. Throughout the week.
Cal: Yeah, and then, like I said, send me any inspiration photos, and then I'll have our team make mood boards, take new photos, I'll get you photos of the missing kitchen, I'll get you as many tile links so you can pick the photos you want out of those, I'll get you everything else that you're missing, and then, like I said, anything inspiration-wise you see, if we don't have it, just send me inspiration photos, because I do have a full design team here, and a full, like, photography team here. Same thing with the interior design website.
Cal: If you have an image, just tell me what you're looking for, and I can have our team build it, and take photos of it, so…
Kyle Lorenzo: For sure. And that's why you guys are, like, my favorite client to work with.
Cal: Yeah, just tell us what you need, and we can pretty much do it, so… Gotcha.
Kyle Lorenzo: All right, sounds good. Well, I appreciate the, the collaboration as always, and yeah, I'll shoot over everything, I'll shoot over… I'll shoot over a couple more things that I might be wanting, so we'll, we'll get this knocked out.
Cal: Awesome, sounds good, we'll talk to you soon.
Kyle Lorenzo: Beautiful. Cool. Awesome. Thank you, Kel. We'll talk soon.
Cal: Alright, bye there.
Kyle Lorenzo: Bye.